[Music]
I am so sorry.
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
Dad, what's going on?
Ah, nothing.
I just got my hand in a chicken.
Yeah, it's dead.
Where are you?
Oh, cool.
Hi.
Hey.
There's a chicken
On your hand.
No, Carly just walked in.
Yeah, sure.
For you.
Who is it?
Our creator.
Dad?
He's on a submarine.
Oh, cool.
Dad, hey.
Yeah, we're doing
iCarly tonight, why?
No way.
How?
How what?
Shh.
Really?
Oh my God, that's so great.
What's great?
Shhh.
So, everyone, on the whole sub?
Every who on the whole what?
Just stuff your chicken.
That's so amazing.
Right, so I guess
I'll see you tonight.
I mean, I won't see you,
But you'll see me.
You know what I mean.
Yeah.
Okay, you wanna talk
To Spencer again?
Yay.
Oh, you don't.
Oh...
Okay, bye.
What?
His submarine's docked
Right off the coast of alaska
Where they have internet access.
So, he and the whole crew
Are gonna watch iCarly tonight.
Fo realz?
Fo yeah.
It's gonna be the first time
He's seen our show live.
And why is your hand
In a chicken?
I got a date.
Who with?
With a real woman.
As opposed to?
I just...
I just mean she's like
A really classy lady.
Get this.
Her name is candice.
Classy.
She's the president
Of her own company.
She reads books,
And she wears pantyhose.
Impressive.
Yeah.
So you're making her dinner?
Uh-Huh.
She wrote in her online profile
That she likes sophisticated men
Who can cook.
So I'm making her dinner,
And I bought these.
Sophisticated?
I guess.
Where'd you get those?
You know socko's cousin,
The optometrist?
Isaac?
Yep.
[Phone ringing]
Ummm, I think
Your cell phone's ringing.
Yeah.
You see it?
[Phone ringing]
Could it be in your chicken?
Aw, man.
Pretty sophisticated.
In five, four, three, two...
Sync by fant0m
www.addic7ed.com
Hey, Carly.
Yeah?
Is it weird if a guy
Grows hair between his toes?
Why? Do you?
No...
Did you see Sam's e-mail?
No, what e-mail?
She's in jail.
What?
What happened?
She was at the jiffy mart
Buying a snack
And a guy cut in front of her.
So she shoved a hot chili dog
Down his pants
And it turns out
The guy was an ambassador
From mexico.
Aw, Sam.
So then what happened?
He yelled,
"Los frijoles calientes
"Quema mis pantalones.
Ohhhhh."
No, I mean, with Sam?
Oh.
The cops showed up
And took her down to juvy.
Awwww.
Her mom's on her way there,
But Sam says there's no way
She's getting out till tomorrow.
So, you're canceling iCarly?
Well, I don't see how we're
Gonna be able to do the show...
No, we're not
Canceling iCarly.
We've never canceled the show.
And my dad's watching it
Live tonight for the first time.
I thought
Spencer was your dad.
Gibby.
Well, how are we gonna
Do the show without Sam?
Spencer.
Normal, here I come.
[Music]
Spencer, Spencer.
Yeah, what's up?
I need you to fill in for Sam
On iCarly tonight.
Why? Where's Sam?
Juvy.
Again?
What'd she do?
She shoved a hot chili dog
Down a foreign
Dignitary's pants.
Senor guttierez?
Yeah, how'd you know?
He tweeted about it.
How come you follow senor...
Please, shut up.
Will you do iCarly with me?
Can't.
But dad's watching tonight.
We have to do it for dad.
You know, I have a date
With candice.
So, reschedule it.
She's already on her way.
Ah, come on.
Just have candice wait down here
Till the show is over.
Or she can come up and watch.
Yeah.
Noooo.
She's a very
Sophisticated woman.
I can't have her thinking
I spend my time
Hanging with teenagers
Doing goofy stuff.
That's like all you do.
Yeah, but I can't
Have her thinking that.
She wears pantyhose.
Please?
This is really important to me.
Any other night,
You know I would,
But this date is...
It's...she's...she's not...no, no.
Carly, don't.
No, don't.
Unicorns and taffy.
Lip gloss.
Okay, okay.
I'll fill in for Sam tonight.
Yay, be upstairs
In four minutes.
Three minutes.
I feel duped.
[Doorbell]
Just a moment.
[Music]
Hello, candice.
Spencer.
Won't you come in?
Thank you.
May I take your coat?
I'm not wearing a coat.
Touche.
What a charming place,
So many toys and things.
Very whimsical.
Well, I have...
I have a teenage sister.
You know teenagers,
What with their whimsical toys
And such.
Spencer.
Oh, that's her now.
Here, why don't you have
Some cucumber water,
And I'll go see
What Carly needs.
Thank you.
Until I return.
I'll be here.
Spencer?
Yes?
I think these are
Pickle slices in the water.
Ah, pickles,
The cucumber's grumpy cousin.
I'm here, when do we start?
45 seconds.
Tell me what I do.
Okay.
Freddie says,
"In five, four, three, two,"
Then points at us.
Then we introduce the show.
Then after that we go
To that wheel over there
And do a bit called
"Put that in your man purse,"
Which you don't know about
But just play along
And you'll figure it out
As we go.
Why doesn't freddie say,
"In five, four, three,
Two, one?"
No one knows.
I know.
No one cares.
Now hurry, take your jacket
And glasses off.
But I look so sophisticated.
This is iCarly.
We don't do sophisticated.
10 seconds.
Now, stand here next to me.
I am.
Shhh.
Ready or not, in five,
Four, three, two.
I'm Carly.
And I'm Spencer,
Filling in for Sam, who's...
...been unexpectedly...
...detained.
Yes, detained.
Now, this is a very special
iCarly tonight,
Because my dad...
Our dad.
He's both our dad's.
We're siblings.
They know that.
My dad, colonel steven shay
Of the united states air force
Is watching iCarly live tonight
From a submarine
Just off the coast of alaska.
I don't think you should
Give away his position.
Uh, I meant
The coast of nebraska.
Yes, deep in the
Nebraskan ocean.
Okay, the first thing
We're gonna do tonight...
...uh, is play
A little game called...
Yay.
Yo.
Yes.
Now, this is a man purse.
It belongs to our
Nasty doorman, lewbert.
So nasty.
Last thursday,
Lewbert threw this man purse
At our technical producer,
Freddie.
It hit me in the neck.
So we're gonna fill it
With something fun.
This way.
I'll go that way.
We're gonna spin this wheel
And whatever it lands on...
...that's the substance
We're gonna pour
Into lewbert's man purse?
Who catches on fast?
Meeeee!
And now it's time to...
Spin that wheel.
Go Spencer.
Well, okay.
Awwwww.
Sour milk.
Ta-Da.
We left this gallon of milk
Out in the sun for two weeks.
Whaa.
Whoah.
Jeez.
Ohh.
Augh.
And now let's open
Lewbert's man purse.
Ewwww.
Ahh.
Go.
Oh, gross.
Augh.
Merry christmas.
Oh, ho-Ho-Ho.
Oh, ho-Ho.
Okay, now we'll
Let that marinate.
Now, please enjoy
Our little friend Gibby
As he teaches us
New vocabulary words
While simultaneously
Brushing his teeth with mustard.
Gibby?
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Candice doesn't know
I'm doing this.
I have to stall her.
Okay, but hurry back.
Will do.
Aah.
No, I know.
Ah-Ha, there you are.
There you are.
I was starting to worry.
Ah, I was just helping
My little sister with an issue.
You know how teenage girls
Can be.
Oh, yes.
What was her problem?
Why don't we sit down?
All right.
Right this way.
Here we are.
That is a purple dress.
Now, why don't you try
Some of these mushroom tartlets?
Oo, I'd love one.
And I'll be right back
After I run upstairs
Just to check...
You know the first time
I ever had a mushroom tartlet?
No, I don't.
Well, I just finished
Business school,
And one of my professors
Invites me to this party
At his condo.
Oh-Ho, professors and condos.
Listen, I'll be right back
After i...
Wait, wait, wait.
So I show up at the party
Dressed casual.
Casual?
Business casual.
But when I get in,
I see it is black tie formal.
So I'm hopelessly underdressed.
No.
Yes.
And then, he says...
Why isn't Spencer back yet?
I don't know,
But Gibby's been doing this bit
For four minutes.
So it's at least an hour
And a half later.
And I come back to the party,
Now dressed appropriately...
Yay, a happy ending.
Now, I really should go upstairs
And check on Carly.
Wait, I'm getting to the part
About the mushroom tartlet.
Are you?
Can I stop?
Spencer's not back yet.
Keep going.
It tastes so bad.
Where have you been?
Candice was telling me
A story about mushroom tartlets
And wouldn't shut up.
Well, hurry up
And put on that cowboy stuff.
Okay, okay.
Cornucopia.
Psst.
Sorry Gibby,
That's all we have time for.
And now...
Hi.
Oh, well hello there,
Farm girl.
You have a squirrel
On your face.
Why, no ma'am.
The only furry thing
Upon my face would be
This a'here mustache.
Really?
Well, excepting for these,
Which is eyesbrow.
Those are baby squirrels.
What?
No ma'am, you've made a mistake,
Part two.
I'm afraid I must reittamerate,
"There ain't nary
No squirrels upon my face."
You're stupid.
Oh.
What's up?
Hi.
[Music]
Ha.
Hey-Hey, hey hey.
Hey.
You just done went
And bit my foot.
Shhhh.
You'll wake up the squirrels
On your face.
There ain't a'no squirrels
On my face.
This concludes
Tonight's installment of...
And now, please enjoy
This pre-Taped,
Super-Slow motion footage
Of Carly shaking her
Very wet hair,
Much like a dog after a swim.
Please don't go
Back downstairs
Till the show's over.
I have to.
Dad's watching.
I want the show to be great.
I'll be back
Up in three minutes.
You said that last time.
I promise.
Eyebrows, yeeowww.
Okay, after the wet
Hair thing,
Play a couple more clips
While I set up for "hey,
What am I licking?"
Okay.
Who's gonna be the licker?
You.
Awesome.
Here I come.
Sorry, it took so long,
But Carly needed...
Aah, aah.
Aah.
Who's hungry?
I am.
Are you all right?
Sure, why? What?
Well, you just tumbled down
A flight of hardwood stairs,
And you're wearing
A big fake mustache.
Oh, yes.
I was just helping Carly
With a biology project
For school.
How's a fake mustache
Tie in with
A high school biology project?
Do you like yams?
Sure.
Good, 'cause I made
A lovely yam puree
With almond butter
To go with our
Roasted stuffed chicken.
How's that sound?
Delicious,
And it smells divine.
Divine.
Now, you sit there.
All right.
And here's some yam puree...
Thank you.
Try it.
Okay.
Mmmmm, the almond butter
Gives it such a rich...
Okay, is it a shoe?
No, no.
Keep guessing.
Ummm, is it a guitar?
No, lick it again.
C'mon, 23 seconds left.
Ummm, um, is it a basket?
Oh, wrong, not a basket.
Listen to your tongue.
My tongue is still numb
From the mustard.
10 seconds.
Oh, uhhh,
Is it a tennis racquet?
Yes.
[Bells ringing]
Wow!
Good licking, gib.
Yeah, baby.
This has been...
Okay.
Coming up next, the englishman
Who was a terrible father
To his two children
Named fuffley and peeta.
Fuffley and peeta!
But for the next two minutes,
Please enjoy this footage
That freddie shot
Of a crazy old man
Screaming at a stop sign.
Playback.
I'm in a hurry,
You red octagonal demon.
Turn green.
What happened to johnny carson?
Answer me that.
...me.
Yay.
What is that sound?
It's your new baby,
Me little brother.
I have no new baby.
But of course you do.
His name is lumpley.
Look, the nanny
Is bringing him now.
Here's baby lumpley.
Yay, yay, yay.
It's my family.
Yay, I live in england.
Baby wumpwee want to have
An english accent.
Yay.
Hay-Hay-Hay.
That is not my child.
Oh.
Remove him.
But sir, you requested,
I bring him.
He is indeed
Your child, father.
Poppycock.
Baby wumpwee wanna do
The poppycock dance.
♪ I want a girl with ♪
♪ a mind like a diamond ♪
♪ I want a girl who ♪
♪ knows what's best ♪
♪ I want a girl with ♪
♪ shoes that cut ♪
♪ and eyes that burn ♪
♪ like cigarettes... ♪
Yay.
Heh-Heh-Heh-Heh-Heh.
Now, baby hungee.
Waaaah.
Someone feed that beast.
Might I also have
Some food, father?
No, floss my toes.
Oh, father.
Get between daddy's toes.
Boo-Hoo.
Floss.
Father, please.
It smells like gorgonzola.
Yay, baby so hungee.
Have some creamed fish.
Yay, hungee, hungee.
Whoa, maaaah.
Creamed fish is bad.
No, no more.
I don't want it.
What is going on here?
Uh-Oh.
Baby was worried
This would happen.
Spencer?
Could you give me
Like five minutes
And I'll be right down?
I've been waiting
Almost a half-hour
Down there by myself.
And what is all this anyway?
It's a live web show,
And we refuse
To break character.
Who is this woman?
Off with her head.
If her head does come off,
Might I please eat it?
I feel it's time
For baby lumpley to have
Some more creamed fish.
Oh.
[Choking sound]
Oh! Oh, good heavens.
Baby lumpley has creamed fish
Stuck in his gullet.
I'll heimlich his tummy.
Uh-Oh.
That wasn't very sophisticated.
You're all freaks.
Come again.
Strumpet.
Bye, bye, pantyhose.
Well, I think that's it
For this unusual episode
Of iCarly.
I love you, dad.
Stay safe.
Yay, yay, yay, hay, hay.
Bye daddy.
Hay, hay, hay.
I'm sorry if this
Embarrasses you.
Wait.
Before we go,
I think baby lumpley wants
Some more creamed fish.
Nooooo.
Ah, baby no like...
Sync by fant0m
www.addic7ed.com
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0